Hello young man
Здравствуйте молодой человек
Hello, not a young man
Здравствуйте не молодой человек
I am from Russia, the city of Volgograd I am from Ukraine, the
Я из России город Волгоград Я из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky I am very pleased, very
город Хмельницкий Очень приятно мне
pleased Well, I understand you Why are
очень приятно Ну понял я вас А почему
you not very pleased, well, because in the
вам не очень приятно ну потому что во
first place, it is not Volgograd that you need
первых не Волгоград надо Сталинград
to say Stalingrad This city was a hero,
говорить Этот город герой был правда его
then why  that's why you are embarrassed by
потом почему вот почему у вас стесняется
Stalin, who made us the victory Why
Сталина который победу сделал нам Почему
Yes, we are not embarrassed we are
Да у нас не стесняется у нас ничего
not embarrassed by anything no one is
не стесняется стесняется никто не
embarrassed in Moscow at least one monument to
стесняется в Москве хоть один памятник
Stalin is in Moscow
Сталину есть в Москве
But this is thanks to
Но это благодаря
your ruler Nikit Sergey Leonid
вашим правителем Никит Сергей Леониду
or else because you have  You already have
или еще потому еще вот у вас У вас уже
Russia Regardless of how old it is Yes,
Россия Независимо сколько там лет Да
why haven’t they erected a monument yet? By the way, they
почему не поставили до сих пор памятник
put it
кстати поставили
in Moscow
в Москве
Why there is no monument in Moscow The
Почему нет памятника в Москве Придет
time will come our grandfathers fought for the Motherland for
время наши деды воевали за Родину за
Stalin you betrayed the memory of your grandfathers in Moscow
Сталина вы предали в Москве память дедов
Yes, you see, you betrayed at least one
Да видать так предали до хоть одного
Stalin street  there is at least one in
улица Сталина у вас хоть одна есть в
Volgograd there is no Stalin street, but there
Волгограде есть улица Сталина нету а
is Lenin street in every
улица Ленина есть правда есть каждом
city Why didn’t you
городе Почему вы в Волгограде не
rename the central Stalin street in Volgograd
переименовали улицу центральную Сталина
Yes, because we are a little smarter than you,
Да потому что мы чуть-чуть поумнее вас
that is, you look at you don’t give a [ __ ] about
то есть вы смотрите вам насрать на
Stalin’s memory
память Сталина
you are sitting you imperiously American
вы сидите вы повелительно американские
popcorn  on American jeans and chewing gum
попкорн на американский джинсы и жвачку
they ruined the Soviet Union on Comrade
развалили Советский Союз на товарища
Stalin, you don’t give a [ __ ] and live
Сталина насрать вам стало и живете
now American phones all
сейчас американский телефоны все
Internets Dollars you have dollars
интернетики Доллары есть у вас доллары
Of course there are Dollars, but there is
Конечно есть вот Доллары есть а
no monument to Stalin and there
памятника Сталину нет а улицы Сталина
is no street of Stalin, and all of you exchanged Stalin’s dollar
нет вот и все вы долларе Сталина
for dollars, you understand Stalin  ate
променяли на доллары понимаете Сталин за
red caviar for you in the Kremlin throughout the war
вас икру красную жрал в Кремле всю войну
And you didn’t want to name the street for
А вы были не хотите ему улицу назвать
him unconsciously sold the memory of where
его бессознательно продали память где
your St.
ваши Георгиевская лента покажите
that I support Ukraine And I
потому что я поддерживаю Украину А я
support Russia My name is Look, I
поддерживаю Россию Меня зовут Смотри у
have refugees like I sheltered at home and
меня живут беженцы типа я дома приютил и
what welcomes you
что чем вас приветствует
because in your Russian Federation
потому что в вашей Российской Федерации
you attacked them you betrayed the Testament of Comrade
напала на них вы предали Завет товарища
Stalin kill Fraternal people we are Czech
Сталина убивайте Братский народ мы Чехии
Slavs and Slavs Ukrainians you sheltered
славяне и украинцы славяне вы приютили
them  And who are you, it’s not clear who
их А вы кто какие-то непонятно кто
says death, that is, you want the death of
смерти говорит то есть вы хотите смерти
Ukrainians We Czechs help Ukrainians
украинцев Мы чехи помогаем украинцам
so that they survive yes And you want to kill
чтобы они выжили да А вы хотите убить
Ukrainians Slavs no no
украинцев славян нет нет
yours There and so on Slavic
ваша Там и так дальше Славянская
turns out yes
получается да
and we ourselves are elephants I Czechoslovakia is a Slav of
а мы себя слоны я Чехословакия славянин
Czechoslovakia Yes
чехослова Да
no  tree why
не дерево почему
I never believed you Why
никогда я вам не поверил Почему
that we are Czechoslovaks we are not Slavs Poles
что чехословаки мы не славяне поляки
Czechoslovaks Serbs Croats Slovenes We are all
чехословаки Сербы хорваты словенцы Все
Slavs And you don’t understand
мы славяне А вы не понятно
I worked with Croats
Я работал с хорватами
Croats Catholics that they are not Slavs from this
хорваты католики что они из этого не
But what is further than the conversation The
Но что дальше в чем разговор
conversation is that we are Czechoslovakian
Разговор в том что мы чехословарь
Ukrainians  Byelorussians Poles Serbs Croats
украинцы белорусы поляки Сербы хорваты
are all Slavs Do you live On the
это все славяне А вы живете На
Caspian Sea live like this somewhere The
Каспийском море живете так где-то
Caspian Sea is closer
Каспийском море ближе
Tatars are
татары
not Slavs We are Slavs further
не славяне мы славяне дальше
we defined us We want to take all
мы нас определили Мы хотим забрать все
our lands
свои земли
our Czechoslovaks, together with other
наша чехословаки вместе с другими
NATO countries, supplies weapons to Ukraine
странами НАТО поставляет Украине оружие
Ukraine look I saw  I don’t know if
Украина смотрите Я видел я не знаю
it’s true or the untruthful Slovaks
правда это или неправдавшие словаки
live
живут
Ukraine has already attacked you in the Belgorod
Украины уже вас атаковала в Белгородской
region
области
And why
А почему
even
даже
Why didn’t you
Почему вы не освободили
free up the time it’s time
освободим время пришло
how much
сколько сколько
and how much you need Well, look, I was in
а сколько вам нужно Ну смотри я в
Czechoslovakia a year ago I thought you would take
Чехословакии год назад думал вы возьмете
Kiev in a couple of days, really, that is  we
Киев за пару дней ну реально то есть мы
all saw how crowds of Russian
все видели эти как толпы российские
armies came in We have Czechoslovakia
армии заходили Мы у нас Чехословакии Да
Yes, the president is a demon, he said everything
вот президент демон он сказал все
let's not support Ukraine
давайте не будем поддерживать Украину
because the Russians are now two days old and they will
потому что русский сейчас два дня и
take it later they didn’t take so
возьмут потом смотрят не взяли взяли так
huge spectators and we have also begun to
огромные зрителей и мы уже тоже начали
support American Biden has arrived
поддерживать Американ байден приехал У
We here in Prague have blocked the streets for a very long time
нас тут в Прагу очень вот перекрыли
By the way, they say that democracy Yes, they
улицы Кстати говорят что демократия Да
blocked the streets You won’t come up so you wo
улицы перекрыли Вот ты не подойдёшь так
n’t say canoe Hello, like they do
байду не скажешь Привет типа они
n’t let random people down
случайных людей не подводят
and agreed and the Czech Republic, too, and other
и договорился и Чехия тоже и другие
NATO countries now support Ukraine
страны НАТО поддерживают теперь Украину
We gave them so many of these
Мы же им дали столько вот этих всяких
they gave a lot of things to all sorts of systems, and now from our look from
много чего дали и вот из нашей смотреть
our equipment they are now dumping
из нашей техники теперь валят по
your Shebekino in the Belgorod region.
Белгородской области вашей Шебекино
In short, here I pay taxes here in the Czech Republic.
Я короче вот я плачу налоги тут в Чехии
Yes, the Czechoslovaks buy their
Да чехословаки и своих налогов покупают
weapons and give them to Ukraine. Ukraine is bombing
оружие отдают Украине Украина бомбит
Belgorod.
Белгород Я считаю что мы налоги идут
I didn’t interrupt you,
Новый человек я вас не перебивал
so you spoke out, you can tell me No
вот высказались можно мне сказать Нет
no again you will
нет опять вы будете говорить
say yes, look, I will listen to you
говорите да смотрите я буду вас слушать
super This is the right strategy water
супер Вот это правильная стратегия вода
The fact is that I will say more with us you
Дело в том что и я больше скажу у нас вы
may not know the plans Ukrainians also don’t
можете не знаете планы украинцы тоже не
know you Zelensky came  Recently,
знают вам Зеленский приезжал вот недавно
our journalists also wrote to Czechoslovakia that during
наши журналисты писали что он на
conversations with the president, this is the
разговорах с президентом вот этим новым
new president we have elected,
у нас новый президент которого избрали
this demon, he was still about the Russian
Этот демон он еще был про российский
a little bit, but he is a NATO general
немножко но он натовский генерал
president, and Zelensky said at a meeting with
президент все и Зеленский на встрече с
him that
ним сказал что
the Belgorod region is not limited
Белгородской областью не ограничиться
there  quickly then it was taken away from these from the
там быстро это потом забрали из этих из
News, you understand that censorship is what
Новостей вы понимаете что цензуры
your name is, in
Вас как зовут
short, it can be somehow abbreviated
покороче можно как-нибудь это сокращенно
if
если
listen to me,
слушай меня
when they start hammering you, you will all
вот когда вас начнут долбить вы все
come and fall in front of Russia So who is
придете упадете перед Россией Так кто
watching
смотрит
and it will be
а это будет будет
traitors
предатели
yesterday cousin you live in Slovakia already
вчера двоюродная живёшь в Словакии уже
why did she get married in the
семидесятого года зачем а замуж вышла в
seventies and lives
семидесятом и живёт
in what city does the sister live in what city does she
в каком городе сестра в каком городе
live
живёт
in Prague
в Праге
just another you don’t know any city
просто другой не знаешь никакой город
other cities
другие города Откуда мне знать
Russia
вышла и уехала нахрен из этой России
well done well done Good strategy Yes she
молодец молодец Хорошо стратегия да она
keeps in touch with you Now I don’t and I
поддерживает с вами связь Сейчас нет и я
Why is pressure interesting that is, she
А почему давление интересно то есть она
thinks she’s an [ __ ] why is he an [ __ ] why did
считает мудаком к чему [__] он почему
she stop communicating with you Yes, I’m not
она перестала общаться с вами Да мне не
interested in her at all Your opinion is not for
интересно она мне вообще ваше мнение не
example
например
Russia Why have
России Почему
you always been humiliated  they killed,
Вас всегда унижали убивали
such a time will come think think
наступит такое время подумай подумай
well that you know the Russian language well you
хорошо что ты знаешь русский язык хорошо
can ride for a Russian we won’t
можно за русского прокатить мы вас не
touch you maybe or maybe touch you Well for
тронем может быть а может и тронет Ну за
your words you can touch And how you find me you will find
свои слова можно тебе и тронуть А как ты
you will find we will find look think
меня найдёшь ты найдешь найдёт найдём
we are behind us  America USA
смотри думаешь у нас за нами Америка США
What do you think America is sitting across
А вы как думаешь Америка сидится за
the ocean And I won’t America your
океаном А мне не Америка будет ваша
Volgograd will take your wake up
Волгоград возьмёт ваш разбудить
Well look at you that you have
Ну смотри у тебя У тебя что у тебя
Russian people who want to take your phone
российские желающие у тебя телефон
you wanted to take you already rise You are already
ваш хотел взять ты уже подымешься Ты уже
under America
под Америкой
look Grandfather you are already under  America Yes,
смотри Дед ты ты уже под Америкой Да
because you have everything even your
потому что у тебя всё у тебя даже
TV is American true Hey, the badge
телевизора американские правда Эй бляха
grandfather ran away switched
дед убежал переключился
[music] a
[музыка]
kilogram right at a time autumn
килограмм прям за раз осень
YouTube driving us through the cardiorka into
YouTube загоняя нас через кардиорке в
the shadow ban and the rich look is not
теневые бан и дужебогатого вида не
shown to people in private,
показывается людям в частном на
information about streams is shown
показывается информация про стримы
therefore, in order to have a little operational
потому для то чтобы мало оперативный
zazok Sign right at a time and try there in a
зазок Подпишите прямо за раз а попыт там
kilogram about Krim video
в килограмме о Крим видео
information and you and I atermata on a
информация и мы с вами атерматы по
stylish
стильной
operational stars we are pledged
оперативной звездок нас заложено
to show you the YouTube word to Ukraine
покажем вам YouTube слово Украине